import { TriviaQuestion } from "../types/trivia";

const triviaQuestions: TriviaQuestion[] = [
  {
    question: "What slayer level is required to kill an Abyssal Demon?",
    answers: ["85"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the highest combat level monster in Old School RuneScape?",
    answers: ["Sol Heredit"],
  },
  {
    question: "What agility level is required to weild the Bow of Faerdhinen?",
    answers: ["70"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "How many marks of grace do you need to purchase the full Graceful outfit?",
    answers: ["260"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "How much slayer points does it cost to unlock the Slayer Helmet?",
    answers: ["400"],
  },
  {
    question: "How much experience is required to reach level 99 in a skill?",
    answers: ["13034431"],
  },
  {
    question: "What is the highest combat level in Old School RuneScape?",
    answers: ["126"],
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the current rank 1 player in Old School RuneScape?",
    answers: ["Lynx Titan"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which Jagex Moderator is commonly know as the god of RuneScape?",
    answers: ["Mod Ash", "Ash"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the full name of the boss you kill at the end of the Inferno?",
    answers: ["TzKal-Zuk"],
  },
  {
    question: "From which creature can you obtain a Dragon Warhammer?",
    answers: ["Lizardman Shaman"],
  },
  {
    question: "From which raid can you obtain the Twisted Bow?",
    answers: ["Chambers of Xeric", "CoX", "Raids 1"],
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the final boss in the Theatre of Blood?",
    answers: ["Verzik Vitur", "Verzik"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which skill allows you to store multiple teleports in a single object?",
    answers: ["Construction", "Con"],
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the final boss in the Chambers of Xeric?",
    answers: ["Great Olm", "Olm"],
  },
  {
    question: "What melee attack style is a gargoyle weak to?",
    answers: ["Crush"],
  },
  {
    question: "How much fishing experience do you gain from catching a shark?",
    answers: ["110"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What increases your odds of getting a bird's nest while cutting a tree?",
    answers: [
      "Woodcutting Skillcape",
      "Woodcutting cape",
      "Wc cape",
      "Wc skillcape",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "How long does a bond last for?",
    answers: ["14 days", "2 weeks"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which Barrows Brother can hit through protection prayers?",
    answers: ["Verac the Defiled", "Verac", "Veracs", "Verac's"],
  },
  {
    question: "What slayer level is required to kill a Jelly?",
    answers: ["52"],
  },
  {
    question: "To which race does Doric belong?",
    answers: ["Dwarf", "Dwarves"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who gives you the ghostspeak amulet during the Restless Ghost quest?",
    answers: ["Father Urhney", "Urhney"],
  },
  {
    question: "Who rules Varrock?",
    answers: ["King Roald", "Roald"],
  },
  {
    question: "What was the city of Varrock originally known as?",
    answers: ["Avarrocka"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What colour of tears should you collect for the Tears of Guthix minigame?",
    answers: ["Blue"],
  },
  {
    question: "Who owns the wood west of Seers' Village?",
    answers: ["McGrubor"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which White Knight is found sitting on a bench in Falador Park?",
    answers: ["Sir Tiffy Cashien", "Tiffy", "Sir Tiffy", "Tiffy Cashien"],
  },
  {
    question: "I wear fancy goggles and a blue party hat, who am I?",
    answers: ["Wise Old Man"],
  },
  {
    question: "In Pest Control, which monster heals the portals?",
    answers: ["Spinner"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the Magic level required to cast the spell 'Ice Barrage'?",
    answers: ["94"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the Ranged level requirement to equip studded leather armour",
    answers: ["20"],
  },
  {
    question: "Wizard boots are a reward from which clue scroll tier?",
    answers: ["Easy"],
  },
  {
    question: "What is commonly known as the 'Red Prison'?",
    answers: ["The Corrupted Gauntlet", "Corrupted Gauntlet", "CG"],
  },
  {
    question: "How many herb patches are there in Old School RuneScape?",
    answers: ["10"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "I sometimes appear to see your account is secure, if it is I leave you a reward. Who am I?",
    answers: ["Count Check"],
  },
  {
    question: "What level is half way to 99?",
    answers: ["92"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the maximum amount of experience you can gain in a skill?",
    answers: ["200 Million", "200m"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the max amount of clan members you are able to have ranked in an Old School RuneScape clan?",
    answers: ["500"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the maximum total level that's achieveable on Tutorial Island?",
    answers: ["56"],
  },
];

export default triviaQuestions;
